好，我马上就走，得赶一班飞机
Yeah, I'll be out here in a minute, I've got a flight to catch
找到了
That's it! I got it.
欢迎来到威奇塔中陆机场
Welcome to Wichita Mid-Continent Airport
便利、友善、价廉 欢迎搭乘
Convenient, friendly, affordable. Fly with us.
请注意，堪萨斯州清净空气法 规定本机场全面禁烟
Please note, the Kansas Clean Air Act has designated this airport as non-smoking.
“美国米德兰航空飞波士顿延误” “美国米德兰航空飞波士顿准时”
旅客请注意
Your attention, please. Baggage claim is located
行李提领处位于航站东侧
on the east side of the terminal.
饭店暨地面交通资讯告示
Hotel and ground transportation information boards
以及公共电话位于行李转盘的对面
and public telephones are located opposite the baggage carousels.
“你死了”
各位女士先生
Ladies and gentlemen, please maintain visual contact
请随时留意个人物品
with your personal property at all times.
请不要留下行李或其他物品无人看管
Please do not leave your baggage or other items unattended.
感谢您的合作
Thank you for your cooperation.
-不好意思 -抱歉
-Excuse me. -Sorry.
我赶得上早一班飞机，对吗？
So, I'm gonna make it onto the earlier flight, right?
行李要拖运吗？
Are you gonna check that?
我会带上机，里面有重要东西
No, I'm gonna carry it on. It's got valuables in it.
-都办好了 -谢谢
-Here you are. -Thank you.
-不好意思 -不，我才抱歉
-God, excuse me. -No, I'm sorry.
那个袋子重到爆
That bag is wicked heavy, anyhow.
我在看手机，我最讨厌别人这么做
I was looking at my phone. I hate it when people do that.
你沾到一点…
You have a little
脏东西
smudge.
这些是什么？
What are these?
是庞帝克引擎用的双腔化油器
Those are two barrel carburetors for a Pontiac Tri-Power.
那些是1974年… 雪佛兰车款的排气管
Those are exhaust tips for a '74 Z-28.
我专门整理旧车…
I restore old cars, so...
吹风机
Hair-dryer.
我的天，真是抱歉
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
撞上瘾了
This is getting to be a habit.
是啊
Yeah, it is.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
-谢谢 -没关系
-Thank you. -Yeah.
-谢谢 -不客气
-Thank you. -Yeah, sure.
去波士顿？
Boston?
对
Yeah.
12号登机门
Gate 12.
一路顺风，贾西亚先生
Enjoy your flight, Mr. Garcia.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉，您不在乘客名单上
I'm sorry. You're not on this flight.
我10分钟前才办好登记
Well, I just checked in for this one, like, 10 minutes ago.
一定是哪里出错了
That must be some sort of mistake.
抱歉，电脑显示我们客满了
I'm sorry, the computer shows that we're booked.
听着，雪莉
Listen, Sharry.
明天我一手带大的小妹要结婚
Tomorrow my little sister's getting married. I practically raised her.
抱歉，座位真的全满了
I'm sorry, we are completely sold out.
你能帮我想想办法吗？我小妹耶
Listen, can you help me out for a second? She's my little sister.
她叫艾波儿，我是茱恩
She's April, I'm June,
她等着我明天陪她走红毯
she's counting on me to march her down the aisle tomorrow.
好温馨
That's very sweet,
搭11点50分的晚班机 您明早就会抵达
but the 11:50 will get you there tomorrow morning with plenty of time.
登机证，先生？
Your boarding pass, sir?
有时事出必有因
Sometimes things happen for a reason.
一路顺风，米勒先生
Enjoy your flight, Mr. Miller.
谢谢
Thank you.
美国米德兰航空77号班机最后登机通知
This is the final boarding call for US Midland Air, flight 77
直飞波士顿洛根机场
non-stop service to Boston's Logan Airport,
请到12号门登机
now boarding at gate 12.
持有效登机证的所有乘客请…
Would all passengers holding a valid boarding pass, please proceed...
我早该料到，他起肖到失控了
I should've seen it coming, boss. He went on tilt, he came undone.
我们这行如果失控大不了喝个几杯
Coming undone in our business means you need a margarita.
不是在政府实验室干掉一票人后
It doesn't mean capping a dozen people in a government lab
再把它炸掉
and blowing it up.
不是就能窃取重大机密
It doesn't mean stealing an object of critical importance.
他到底有没有偷走赛佛？
Does he have the Zephyr or not?
我们相信有
We believe so.
你相信有
You believe so.
看一下
Check it out.
我不在乎你相信什么，费兹
I don't care what you believe, Fitz.
收拾好你的烂摊子
I need you to clean your mess up.
倒带再放一次
Go back and play it again.
我要拿到赛佛
I want the Zephyr.
我们会在他抵达波士顿时拿到手
We'll have it in hand by the time he lands in Boston.
查出她的身分和背景
Find out who and what she is.
要请威奇塔的分处逮捕她吗？
Should I have the field office pick her up in Wichita?
我有更好的主意
I got a better idea.
赫文斯小姐
Miss Havens?
我们替您找到机位了
We did find a seat for you.
请注意，抱歉延误起飞
I'd like to have your attention, please. We apologize for the delay.
我们很快会从威奇塔机场出发
We will be departing Wichita Airport shortly.
“移动，警告”
感谢您的耐心
Thanks for your patience.
“艾玛波拉路5826号”
我知道你只是依照公司政策做事
I know it's policy or whatever and it's just your job,
但这实在有点瞎
but it's kind of lame.
真是抱歉
Again, I apologize.
费兹，你动了什么手脚？
Fitz. What did you do?
难怪航空公司会倒
It's no wonder these airlines are going out of business.
飞机上只有小猫两三只
We have been cleared onto the runway. There's nobody on the plane.
机长已开殷系好安全带指示灯
The captain has turned on the "fasten seatbelt" sign.
请坐在位置上直到指示灯熄灭
Please remain seated until the sign has been turned off
才能在机舱内走动
and it's safe to move about the cabin.
对了，我是茱恩
I'm June, by the way.
我是罗伊米勒
I'm Roy Miller.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
彼此彼此
It's very nice to meet you.
龙舌兰加冰块？
Tequila on the rocks?
好，正是时候，谢了
Yeah. Just in time, thanks.
所以你小妹明天结婚？
So, your sister's getting married tomorrow?
-什么？ -你小妹
-Excuse me? -Your sister.
她明天结婚，恭喜
She's getting married tomorrow. Congratulations.
是啊，谢了
Yeah, thanks.
罗伊，我不善于说谎
You know, Roy, I'm a bad liar.
抱歉，怎么说？
I'm sorry, how's that?
艾波儿要结婚，不过是周六
April is getting married, but not till Saturday.
你唬到我了
You had me fooled.
可是我明天要试装
Well, I do have a fitting tomorrow.
所以我真的得回家
So, I do, actually, have to go home.
希望这趟飞行别太难熬
I hope this isn't gonna be a rough flight.
很难说
It might be.
跑来威奇塔买化油器还真远
Wichita is a long way to go for a carburetor.
这可不是一般的化油器
It's not just any carburetor.
是三段式化油器
It's a triple deuce.
我在整理1966年的GTO
I'm restoring a '66 GTO.
堪萨斯州有最棒的零件厂
And Kansas has the best scrap.
真的？
Really?
我爸开修车厂
My dad had a garage,
我小时候，他买了这台车的底盘
and when I was a kid, he bought this chassis.
他经常带我们到处找零件
He used to take us to yards, and search for parts, you know?
他于1998年过世，如今艾波儿结婚
He died in '98, and now that April's getting married
我心想，何不把车整理好？
I just figured, why not finish it up,
送她当作结婚礼物
give it to her sort of as a wedding present?
也算是老爸送的礼物
Kind of like a present from our dad, too, you know?
好感人
That's nice.
-是啊 -是啊
-Yeah. -Yeah.
我常想
I used to think that
有朝一日，当最后的零件装上
someday, when the last part went in,
我会爬进那台车，发动它
I would just climb into that GTO and start it up.
一股劲儿地开，不停地开
Just drive and drive and drive, and just keep driving
直到抵达南美洲的尽头
until I got to the tip of South America.
合恩角
Cape Horn.
对
Yeah.
那里有美丽的岛屿
There's beautiful islands down there.
是吗？
Yeah?
海盗岛
Pirate islands.
“有朝一日”是个危险字眼
Yeah, "someday." That's a dangerous word.
危险？
Dangerous?
它其实只是“永不”的代名词
It's really just code for "never."
我常在想我还有什么事没做过
I think a lot about things I haven't done.
在大堡礁潜水，乘上东方快车
Dive in the Great Barrier Reef. Ride the Orient Express.
住在阿玛菲海岸
Live on the Amalfi Coast
只有摩托车和背包相伴
with nothing but a motorcycle and a backpack.
在海角酒店阳台亲吻陌生人
Kiss a stranger on the balcony of the Hotel Du Cap.
那在哪里？
Where is that?
南法
South of France.
那你呢？
What about you?
你想做哪些事？
What's your list?
这个嘛…你的听起来很不赖
Well, yours sounds pretty good.
天啊
Wow.
谢了
Thanks.
别客气
It's no problem.
不介意的话我放在这里
I'll just put this up here, if that's all right.
不好意思
You know what?
我要去化妆室整理一下
I'm gonna go back and use the restroom.
我帮你
I'll help you.
谢了
Thanks.
乱流真多
Lots of turbulence, huh?
-我马上出来 -没问题
-I'll be out in a minute. -Sure
“在海角酒店阳台亲吻陌生人”
"Kiss a stranger on the balcony of the Hotel Du Cap"?
这是什么台词？
I mean, what kind of a line is that?
太浪漫了
I mean, it's, like, a really good line.
小姐？小姐？
Ma'am? Ma'am?
你有没有看见他的手？
Did you see his hands, by any chance?
一下子就接住袋子
They just, like, snatched that bag right out of the air.
超快的反射动作
Lightning-fast reflexes.
太不上道
Not cool.
好
Okay.
这会有帮助
This will help.
够了，结束了，罗伊
Enough. It's over, Roy.
我同意，够了
Yeah, I agree. Enough.
赛佛在哪里？
Where's the Zephyr?
那女的为什么在机上？快说
Why is the girl on the plane? Tell me.
为什么费兹安排她上机？
Why did Fitz put her on the plane?
别动，米勒
Don't move, Miller.
好，你打算怎么做？ 你打算怎么做？
So what are you gonna do? What are you gonna do?
你打算让这机会溜掉？
You're just gonna let this opportunity pass you by?
不，当然不行
No, of course you're not.
你要走出去，主动一点
You're gonna walk right through that door, you're gonna get it right.
反正你也不是第一次主动
It's not your first rodeo, woman.
嗨
Hey.
我决定也来一杯
I decided to join you.
抱歉，我…
I'm sorry. I...
不，没关系…这样很棒
No, no, don't... It's great.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
龙舌兰和在高空都会令人兴奋
It's just, like, the tequila and the altitude and everything.
我得告诉你一件事
There's something I've gotta tell you.
什么？天啊，你有女朋友了
What? Oh, my God, you're in a relationship.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不是，不是那样
No, no, no. That's not it.
不是？我洗耳恭听，是啥？
Okay, I'm all ears. What is it?
我们要降落了吗？
Are we landing?
还没
No, not yet.
还没？
No?
听着，不需要惊慌
Listen, there's no need to panic.
我已经…控制情况
I have contained the situation.
情况？
Situation?
对，我们…失去了机长
Yeah. We've lost the pilots.
他们去哪了？
Where did they go?
应该是说他们死了
I mean, they're dead.
-机长死了 -被射杀
-The pilots are dead. -Shot. It's...
被射杀？
Shot?
谁干的？
By who?
就是我
Well, me.
实际上我杀了正驾驶
Actually, I shot the first pilot.
他意外杀了副驾驶
He shot the second pilot accidentally.
你懂…
It's just
就是这么回事
one of those things.
说真的，这个好笑！
Seriously, this is great!
我大可放心了，你好镇静
Really, I'm relieved you are taking this so well.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
我去看一下，想办法降落
I'm just gonna go check on things and think about landing.
能帮个忙系上安全带吗？
Would you mind putting your seatbelt on for me?
-那就太好了 -好
-That would be great. -Yeah.
太诡异了
This is weird.
求救，求救
Mayday. Mayday.
美国米德兰航空77号班机
This is US Midland Air 77 heavy.
这是怎么回事？
What's happening?
机内每个人真的都死了！
Everybody's dead out there!
过来，坐下
Come on in. Sit down.
求救，求救，求救
Mayday, mayday, mayday.
这里每个人都死了
Everybody's dead in here.
这是紧急事件
I'm declaring an emergency.
我的天啊！我们会坠机吗？
Oh, my God! Are we going down?
什么？
I'm sorry?
我们会坠机吗？
Are we going down?
茱恩，只是快速下降，请坐下
No, June, it's just a rapid descent. Please, sit down.
抱歉，我想我听够这家伙了
I'm sorry, I think I've heard enough of this guy.
你是飞行员吗？你是谁？
Are you a pilot? Who are you?
肩带
The shoulder straps.
把这个戴好
You can put those over,
从右边扣在座位上
and it clicks in right down there.
要扣在那里，没错
You wanna click it right there, that's it.
好，我弄好了
Okay, I got it, I got it. Okay...
放下起落架，慢下来
Gear down, showdown.
我们干嘛不降落在机场？
Why can't we just land in an airport?
不，最好不要
No, no, that wouldn't be a good idea.
他们会等着我们
They'll be waiting for us.
什么意思？等着我们？谁？
What do you mean? Waiting for us?  Who?
我想你知道愈少愈好
I think the less you know, the better.
什么？
What?
好，我们要在这里降落了
Okay, we're gonna touch down here.
天啊！
Oh, God. Oh, my God!
-有卡车，有卡车！ -好
-That's a truck. That's a truck! -Yeah.
-有卡车！ -没错
-That's a truck! -Yup.
有卡车！
That's a truck!
我的天啊！我的天啊！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-有弯路，有弯路！ -我看到了
-That's a curve. That's a curve! -I see it. I see it.
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Oh, God!
太好了
Okay, this is good.
哪里好？
What's good?
喝一口
Take a sip of that.
可以放松一下
It'll take the edge off.
你中弹了？
Are you shot?
对，免骛啦
Yeah, how about that?
只是擦伤，这是好消息
It's just a scrape. That's good news.
茱恩，我们需要…
June, we have to
讨论下一步
discuss what's gonna happen next.
你需要去医院，不然去监狱？
You need to go to the hospital. Prison, maybe?
有些人会来找你，坏人
Some people are gonna come looking for you now. Bad people.
我感觉怪怪的
You know, I feel a little weird.
对，过几分钟你就会昏倒
Yeah, that'll pass once you fall asleep, which should be in a couple of minutes.
-什么？ -我要你听好
-What? -I need you to listen, June.
你对我下药？
Did you drug me?
对
Yes.
-你对我下药 -对，为了你着想
-You drugged me. -Yeah, it's for your own good.
这些坏人会找上你，他们会问起我
Now, look. These bad people who are going to come and see you, they're gonna ask you about me. Okay?
你得回答你不认识我
And you need to tell them you don't know me.
莱恩？
-June? June? -Okay.
你得说你什么都不记得
You need to tell them you don't remember anything.
你无论如何要避免上他们的车
And you need to avoid getting in any vehicle with them at all costs.
好，  “他们”是谁？
Okay, who are "them"?
他们是狠角色
Well, they're serious people, June.
他们会自称是联邦调查局探员
They'll probably identify themselves as federal agents,
他们会误导你
and they'll DIP you.
误导我怎样？
Dip me? In what?
反情报规则，他们会瞎掰我的事
Dis-Information Protocol. They'll tell you a story about me.
说我精神不稳定、有妄想症
About how I'm mentally unstable, paranoid.
暴力又危险
How I'm violent and dangerous,
听起来都很像真的
and it'll all sound very convincing.
我已经被说服了
I'm already convinced.
一些基本的关键字会出现
There's a few common DIP keywords to listen for.
安慰的字眼
Reassuring words. Words like,
比如稳定、确保、安全
"stabilize," "secure," "safe."
只要他们提到这些字眼
If they say these words,
尤其重覆时…
particularly with repetition...
好
Okay.
这表示他们会杀了你
...it means they're going to kill you.
天啊！
Oh, God!
或者把你长期关到境外某处
Or intern you somewhere offshore for a very long time.
-懂吗？ -懂
-Okay? -Okay.
仔细听我说，只要他们说你很安全…
Now, stay with me. If they tell you you're safe...
如果他们说我很安全
If they tell me I'm safe,
他们会杀了我
they're gonna kill me.
别上什么？
Don't get in what?
上车
Vehicles.
任何车
Any vehicles.
好，任何车
Okay, any vehicles.
-要快点逃 -我会逃
-Just run. -I'll run.
快逃-快逃
-Run. -Run.
要是他们问起我…
And if they ask you about me...
我不认识你
I don't know you.
我完全不认识你
I don't know you at all.
罗伊，你到底是谁？
Who are you, Roy?
“茱恩，很高兴认识你，罗伊”
…混着雨和雪，适合滑雪区
... a mixing of rain and snow, good for ski country, but probably...
“吃顿丰盛早餐，茱恩”
-谢了，安卓 -不答气
-Thanks, Andrea. -You're welcome.
接着回到今早的头条新闻
Now, back to our top news story of the morning.
布莱德利摩斯在现场报导
Here's Bradley Moss, with an on-the-scene report.
根据联邦航空局的消息 昨晚约7点半时
According to FAA sources, at approximately 7:30 last night,
与威奇塔飞往波士顿的一架客机 失去所有联系
all contact was lost with a Boston-bound commuter jet from Wichita.
这架飞机显然飞经不稳定气流
The plane was apparently passing through an area of turbulence
可能遭乱流或闪电影响
and may have met up with wind shear
造成断电
or a lightning storm causing an electrical failure.
目前一切都还是推测
Now, this is all conjecture at this point,
证据只有… 在印地安那州玉米田中的残骸
as all that's left is a crater in an Indiana cornfield.
来了
Coming!
“记得，别告诉任何人”
罗德尼？
Rodney?
谢天谢地，我想确定你安然无恙
Thank God. I wanted to make sure you were okay.
怎么了？
Yeah, why?
你不是昨天从堪萨斯飞回来？
You were on that flight from Kansas, right?
-对 -我看新闻说坠机了
-Yeah. -I saw on the news about the crash.
什么新闻？什么坠机？
What news? What crash?
-没事了，你活着就好 -我活着没错
-Anyway, you're alive. -I'm alive, yeah.
-我看到了，太好了 -茱恩，我在想…
Sure, that's cool. Hey, but, June, you know...
我告诉自己，只要得知你活着
I told myself that if I found you alive,
我要邀你共进晚餐
that I was gonna ask you to dinner.
罗德尼，人分手以后 就不应该再约会
Rodney, people, when they break up, they're not supposed to have dates
那就别说是约会 说消防检查好了
so don't call it a date. Call it a fire inspection!
我晚点打给你好吗？
How about I call you later, okay?
不要告诉别人我在说什么
Don't tell anybody. What I'm talking about.
只是又一天，平常的一天，没事
It's just another day. It's just a normal day. Okay.
威尔莫，我有好东西
Hey, Willmer. I've got some goodies.
天啊，你拿到化油器了
Jesus, you got the deuce
威尔莫，当我回来时会来拿
Will, I'll grab it when I get back in
没事，只不过又是一天
Everything's OK! It's just another day
没事
Nothing happened.
目标移动中
She's moving.
天啊！
Wow!
靴子真是可爱
And gotta love the boots.
不好意思
Yeah, you know.
我保证当天会穿高跟鞋
I promise I'll wear heels on the day.
-能跟你谈一下吗？ -好
-Hey. Can I talk to you for a second? -Yeah.
这个周末，我想到爸的庞帝克
So, this weekend, I was thinking about Dad's GTO.
-真的？ -对，就一直停在车库里
-Really? -Yeah, it's just sitting there.
我想问你愿意卖掉它吗？
And I was wondering how you would feel about maybe selling it.
你想卖掉爸的庞帝克？
You wanna sell Dad's GTO?
我和班很想拥有自己的家
Ben and I, we really want our own place.
请问一下？
Excuse me?
请问一下 外面那台蓝色货车是谁的？
Excuse me. Anyone here belong to that blue truck parked outside?
-是我的，怎么了？ -你快被开罚单了
-Yeah, why? -You're about to get a ticket.
-我以为钱有投够 -嗯
-Thought I put enough quarters in there. -Yeah.
我最讨厌接到罚单
I hate getting tickets.
不好意思
Excuse me.
请跟我们上车，小姐
Please step inside, miss.
我去拿些东西
Let me just go grab a few things.
赫文斯小姐，午安 我是费兹杰罗探员
Miss Havens, good afternoon. Special Agent-in-Charge, Fitzgerald.
请跟我们上车
Will you join us inside the car for a moment?
我们知道昨晚你跟他在飞机上
We know you were on the flight with him last night.
坠机的那架
The one that crashed.
你们到底是谁？
Who are you again?
联邦调查局，你认识米勒先生
FBI. You do know Mr. Miller.
我不认识
No, I don't.
“威奇塔机场摄影机”
这个嘛 我们在过安检时聊了一下，可是…
Well, we chatted a little bit before security, but...
我懂，那登机复发生什么事？ 继续聊天？
I see. And once you were on the flight, what happened then? More chatting?
不，我…
No, I eh...
不算，我喝了一杯，然后…
No, not really, I had a drink, and...
然后就醉倒了
And I was out
他是谁？
Who is he?
直到一周前
Until a week ago
罗伊米勒都还是世界上 最受信任、最能干的探员
Roy Miller was the most trusted, incapable covered agent
一周前出了什么事？
What happened a week ago?
赫文斯小姐，这些事恕我无法奉告
Miss Havens,
就说他承受巨大压力好了
Let's just say, stress caught up with him.
一开始是不信任同僚的指令
It started with the untrust of fellow agent command
之后变成与现实脱节
and it grew until a full break with reality
但他很有魅力
Well, he was very charming
不过只在我还清醒的时候啦
while I wasn't getting out
一下子很有魅力 一下子又嗜杀成性
Charming one moment, homocide the next
-我的问题很好笑？ -不是
-Is this funny to you? -No.
赫文斯小姐，他很危险又失控了
He's dangerous, Miss Havens, and out of control.
他说你会说他疯了
He said that you'd say he was crazy.
这表示你们交谈过，还正好谈到我
So, you did talk to him. And about me, no less.
不，我们谈论的不是你
No. No, not you, specifically.
那是谁？
About whom, then?
赛门费克？
Simon Feck?
我不知道那是谁
I don't know who that is.
事情愈描愈黑了 我想我可能该找个律师
Look, this is getting really twisted around, and I think I should probably call a lawyer.
抓到米勒前，我们会将你安置好
We're gonna take you to a secure location, Miss Havens, until Miller is contained.
一个安全的地方
Someplace safe.
-跟你一起？ -是，女士
-With you? -Yes, ma'am.
各位，能透露我们要去哪里吗？
You wanna tell me where we're going?
别担心，你很安全
-Fellas? -Don't worry, miss, you're safe.
什么？
Excuse me?
你跟我们在一起很安全
You're safe with us.
我想知道我们要去哪里
I wanna know where we're going.
只是个过渡期，直到情况稳定
Just a shortcut till the situation is stabilized.
我们会维护你的安全
We'll keep you safe.
你说过很多遍了
You said that already.
因为我是认真的
Because I meant it.
杰克森在干嘛？
What is Jackson doing?
枪手！枪手！回避！回避！ 高速公路上有枪手
Shooter! Shooter! Evade! Evade! Shooter on the freeway.
你背后有红点！
The dot's on your back!
快跟着我！
Follow me, now!
你疯了吗？我才不跟你跳！
Are you insane? I'm not going out that door!
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
别踩…
Get your foot off...
-我的天啊！ -茱恩！
-Oh, my God! -Hey, June!
-我看不到！ -你表现得很棒
-I can't see! -You are doing great.
-别挡住！ -开门
-I can't see! Get out of the way! -Open the door.
我无法把他的脚移开油门
-I can't get his foot off the gas. -Open the door, June.
开门，对了，衣服很漂亮喔
Open the door, June. That's a beautiful dress, by the way.
等一下
One second.
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
我完全知道你在说什么
I totally know what you're talking about.
真无趣，我根本无法忍受， 一点也没办法
It's so boring, I can't even stand it. Totally.
谢谢
Thank you.
你是怎么做到的？
How did you do that?
-你在干嘛？ -不要慢下来
-What are you doing? -Don't slow down!
不行啊
I can't
你到底是谁？
Who are you?
-嗨，茱恩 -别挡住，我看不到！
-Hi, June. -Move out of the way, I can't see!
请打开车锁，茱恩
Please unlock the door, June.
解锁 那样我才能帮你
Unlock the door. That way, I can help you.
-我不行放手！ -你需要放手，茱恩
-I can't let go! -You need to let go, June.
-茱恩，开门！ -开了！
-June, door! -Got it!
靠边停！我的天啊！
Just pull over! Oh, my God!
过来…对，过来这里
Come on. Come on. Come on. Yup, come over here.
就是这里，蹲下，你表现很好
Right over here. Just stay down, you're doing good.
拿着…好极了
Here, hold this. Well, well, well.
看这些玩意
Check this out.
正点
Nice.
这些家伙有备而来
These guys are loaded for bear.
表现很好，茱恩
You're doing well, June.
开车技术一流，何况车上还有死人
Excellent driving. Over a dead guy, no less.
你是天生好手
You're a natural.
礼服很美
That's a beautiful dress.
是艾波儿的伴娘服吗？
Is that for April's wedding?
-周六？ -对
-Saturday? -Yeah.
-一定很棒 -是啊
-Yeah, that will be nice. -Yeah.
拜托…别再杀人了，好吗？
Please, stop shooting people, okay?
别再杀人了
Just stop shooting people.
我了解
I understand.
你吓坏了
You're in shock.
不如你待在这里
How about you stay here
我去跟隧道里的人哈拉一下，好吗？
while I go have a word with the guys in the tunnel.
好
-Okay? -Okay.
-好吗？ -好
其实我是要去杀了他们，马上回来
Actually, I'm just gonna go shoot them. I'll be right back.
对了，你开车门的时间点…
By the way, your timing when you opened that door...
-好 -很到位
-Okay. ...was sublime.
你救了我们俩，希望你知道
You saved us, I hope you know that.
-你救了我们 -好
-You saved us. -Okay.
等一下
Hey, wait!
等等！
Wait! Wait!
等等…！
Wait!
不妙
Oh, no.
不好意思，抱歉
Excuse me, sorry.
找到你了
There you are.
茱恩？
June?
罗德尼？
Rodney?
他在健身房，在那边
He's in the gym. Over there.
-嗨！ -嗨！
-Hey! -Hey!
你来这里干嘛？
What are you doing here?
各位，跟茱恩打招呼，衣服真漂亮
Whoa! That's a... Hey, guys, say hello to June. That's a dress.
谢了
Thanks.
-一切都还好吧？ -还好
-Everything all right? -Yeah.
不，其实…
No, it's...
有点复杂
It's complicated.
说真的，我有同感
You know what? I've been feeling the same way.
想谈谈吗？
You wanna talk?
或许吃个派？
Maybe over some pie?
我的重点是…
My point is...
我的重点是坠机事件令我想起…
My point is, that plane crash made me think
我们的分手
about our break-up.
我突然就开窍了！
You know, this bulb went off, bing!
罗德尼，你怎么可以放弃？
"Rodney, why are you giving up?
你太消极了
You're being passive."
因为她不想结婚就怨恨她
"Getting back at her because she didn't want the ring."
就算茱恩现在不想订婚
"So June didn't want to be engaged right now,
让你老妈不安，又怎样！
"and that freaks your mom out. Big deal!
那你们的共同计划呢？
"What about all the things you and June wanted to do together, huh?"
那些清单上的事？
Our list, you know?
比如跟我弟和希拉 坐他们的新拖车去佛蒙特州露营
Like camping in Vermont with my brother and Sheila in their new Winnie.
看蓝人团体表演，战场模拟体验
Tickets to Blue Man Group, the battlegrounds tour.
我想谈谈坠机的事
I wanna talk about the plane crash. Okay?
当然，什么事？
Sure, what about it?
我在那上面
I was on it. I mean, in it.
我是说在飞机里
I mean, I was in it.
所以坠机时你在场？
So you were in the plane crash?
我本来不应该在飞机里的 但还是搭上了
I wasn't supposed to be on that plane, but I was on it,
然后有个男人…某种特务
and there was this guy who was some sort of secret agent or something, and he...
他杀掉机上每个人
He killed everybody on board.
然后他把飞机降落
And then he landed the plane.
接下来
Next thing you know,
我在我房间里醒来
I wake up, I'm in my room.
我不知道我怎么回去的
I have no idea how I got there.
他一定对我下药
He must've drugged me or something.
然后我去试穿伴娘服
Then I go to April's fitting,
因为我得穿这么瞎的衣服
because I have to wear this ridiculous dress.
之后其他探员来绑架我
These other guys, these other agents come, they snatch me up.
转眼间
Next thing you know,
我就陷入州际公路的飞车追逐
I'm in Grand Theft Auto on the l-93.
你干嘛碰我的手？
Why are you touching my hand?
因为我想帮你
Because I'm here for you.
-老天，你压力太大了！ -没错！
-Jeez, you are so stressed out! -Well, yeah!
-我懂 -真的？
-And I get it. -Really?
我完全了解
I completely understand. I mean...
-天啊，茱恩 -我了
-Wow, June. -I know.
你小妹要结婚了
-Your little sister's getting married... -It's like...
你备感压力
...and that is stressful.
你在说什么？你没听进我的话
What are you talking about, Rodney? You didn't even listen to what I was talking about.
我有，换作是我可能也半斤八两
No, I did. Look, I would probably be the same way in that situation.
我能怎么帮忙？搭场地？
What can I do to help? Setting up?
我能找人来…
We can bring the guys over...
不…
No, no, no. Okay.
要命
Oh, Christ.
嗨，茱恩，听着
Hi, June. Look, I...
抱歉打断你们
I'm sorry if I'm interrupting anything, but...
我是罗伊米勒
I'm Roy Miller.
罗德尼布里斯
Rodney Burris.
罗德尼，你好
Rodney, hi. How are you?
我们没时间了
We're running out of time,
或许我表达得不够清楚
and maybe I didn't make it clear enough,
但我们得暂时一起行动 因为我们的…
but we're gonna have to stick together for a little bit, because of our...
我们的…情况
You know, our situation.
提醒你一下，罗德尼是消防员
In case you didn't notice, Rodney is a fireman, okay?
他十分擅长处理任何意外情况
So he's perfectly capable of handling any situation that comes up.
感激不尽，你可以走了
Thank you very much, you can leave us alone.
我毫不怀疑
I have no doubt.
从小我就非常崇拜消防员
Ever since I was a little kid, I have great respect for firemen.
感恩
-I appreciate it. -Fact of the matter is,
事实上我觉得你们薪水太低
I don't think you guys get paid enough.
说得好
Yeah, we don't.
你在第10分队
You're in Engine 10.
对，第10分队
Yeah, Engine 10.
你考过中尉测验吗？
Yeah. Have you taken your lieutenant's exam yet?
我正在准备
I'm working on it.
是吗？顺利吗？
Yeah? How's that going?
很难考
It's a bitch.
你有去过那个叫什么厅的？
Did you ever do a tour in that hall, what is it?
古鲁夫厅，非常繁忙的地方
Grove Hall, that's where the action is.
但也升得很快
It's the fastest way up the ladder.
-罗德尼！ -那里是火焰殿堂！
-Rodney! -House of Flames!
我经常想我应该…
I often thought I...
应该成为消防员
I should have been a fireman.
罗德尼，我讲的就是他
Rodney, this is the guy.
什么？
What?
就是这家伙
This is the guy.
什么，就是这家伙吗？
What? "This is the guy"?
抱歉，你是谁？
I'm sorry, who are you?
我就是那家伙？
I'm the guy?
-我就是那家伙 -就是这家伙
-I'm the guy. This is the guy. -This is the guy.
-就是这家伙 -我就是那家伙
-This is the guy. -I'm a guy.
-就是我没错 -就是你没错
-I'm the guy. -You are a guy.
-就是我 -就是他！
-I'm a guy. -He's the guy! He's the guy!
罗德尼，不管发生什么事
-Rodney, whatever happens... -God.
-为了你自身安全 -罗德尼，不管发生什么事
-Please, for your own safety... -Rodney, whatever happens,
请待在座位上
-you should know... ...please stay in the booth.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
等等！
Wait!
所有人趴下
Everybody! Everybody get down.
趴下…！所有人趴下
Get down, down, down! Everybody down.
罗德尼趴下，否则我会轰掉她的头
Rodney, get down, or I will blow her head off.
我会轰掉她的头
I'll blow her head off.
我是怎么说的？
What did I say?
罗德尼，我怎么说的？
Rodney, what did I say?
-冷静，老兄 -回答我！
-Just calm down, buddy. -Answer!
抱歉，我以为你要动手
Sorry, I thought you were making a move.
抱歉，没事，我以为他要动手
Sorry. It's all right, I thought he was making a move.
做一些派给大家吃
Making a little pie. Pies for everybody. Everybody.
人人有份，但不加冰淇淋
Everybody gets pies, okay? No ice-cream, à la mode.
吃冰会腿软，问林肯就知道
Weakens the legs, people. Lincoln knew it.
他就是腿软被干掉
It's why they got to him.
谁都不准跟着我们
No one follows us,
否则我会自杀再干掉她
or I kill myself and then her.
请上车
Get in the car. Please.
不要
No.
小心头
Watch your head.
我们在哈里斯街
We're at 560 Harris.
他们开蓝色富豪车
They're getting into a blue Volvo.
罗德尼！罗德尼！
Rodney! Rodney!
罗德尼？
Rodney?
我的天啊！罗德尼！
Oh, my God! Rodney!
别怕，看着我
It's okay. Look at me.
-看着我，别怕 -该死！
-Okay. Look at me, it's okay. -Shit!
子弹直接穿过
I shot you through and through.
骨头、股动脉都没事
No bone, nowhere near the femoral artery, okay? All right?
这比挤进古鲁夫厅有效，赞啦
This is gonna be better for you than Grove Hall. It's all good.
好吗？你没事吧？
Okay? You good?
-没事？ -没事
-Good? -Good.
没事？
Good?
那间餐厅有四台保全摄影机
There were four security cameras in that restaurant, June.
证据显示你是我的人质
Now there is proof you're my hostage.
你不会被怀疑是歹徒
So we've cleared your name, with the locals, at least.
这是开始，之后会渐入佳境
You know? It's a start. Something to build on.
你对罗德尼开枪！
You shot Rodney!
没错
Yeah, I did.
但我有叫他待在座位上
But I asked him to stay in the booth.
你对罗德尼开枪！
You shot Rodney!
这可能是他遇过最好康的事
It might be the best thing that ever happened to him.
最好是，人一生都该挨个几枪！
Yeah, right, because we all should get shot every now and then!
罗德尼…
Rodney...
罗德尼是好人，茱恩
Rodney is a good guy, June.
但不太适合你
But not really right for you.
纯粹个人想法，不过他是好人
I mean, you know, in my opinion. But a good guy.
挨子弹会让他变英雄
Took a bullet, he's gonna be a hero.
可能会升职
Probably get a promotion.
停车
-Stop the car. Stop the car. -What?
停车，停车，快停车！
Stop the car. Stop the car. Stop the car. Just stop the car!
茱恩，我了解你不想淌这浑水
June, I understand you want off the carousel.
没错，我不想淌这浑水
I do, I wanna get off the carousel. Please, Roy.
罗伊，拜托停车，马上！
Can you stop the car, please? Right now!
我不是那种小心眼的人
I'm not one of those "I told you so" kind of guys,
但我有警告过你别上飞机
but I did warn you to stay off the plane last night.
什么时候？
When?
当我说“有时事出必有因”
Well, when I said, "Sometimes things happen for a reason."
那是什么鬼警告
That's not a warning.
那不算警告，罗伊！
That's not a warning, Roy!
那跟汽车上的贴纸一样没用
That's like a needlepoint expression or a bumper sticker.
下次你该说… 茱恩，上飞机你就死定了！
Next time, try, "June, if you get on this plane, you will fucking die!"
之前那些人可能真的要保护我
You know, Roy, maybe they meant it when they said that I would be safe.
你当真？
You really mean that, June?
对！
Yeah!
你跟他们在一起时感到安全？
Did you feel safe with them?
比现在安全！
Safer than I do now!
好，好吧
Okay, okay. All right.
你最好明白
Just so you understand,
不跟我，你的寿命大概这样
right now, out there, on your own, your life expectancy is like here.
跟着我，在这里，不跟我，在这里
With me, it's here. Without me, here.
跟着我，不跟我，跟着我，不跟我
With me, without me. With me, without me.
所以…
So...
我不建议你回家，但由你决定
I wouldn't advise going home. But, you know, it's up to you.
现在我需要另一台车，走吧
So right now I need another car, keep moving.
有个正有生命危险的人在等我
Someone else is depending on me. Someone whose life is in danger.
他信任我，我多浪费一秒保护你
Someone who trusts me. Every second I waste chasing you,
都是在让他失望
I'm letting him down.
“移动，警告”
“艾玛波拉路5826号”
罗德尼
Rodney,
你怎么这么勇敢？
why did you make this brave call to leap into action?
我没有想太多
Well, I didn't think.
大多数人当下都会这么做的
I just did what any man would do in that situation, you know?
我就跟着冲出去了
-I leapt into action. -Thanks.
如你所说，或许是多年训练的反应
Like you said, it's really the job.
你该引以为傲
You should be so proud.
-谢了 -做得好
-Thanks. -Good job.
这只是小伤，像被蜜蜂螫到
It really didn't even hurt. It was kind of like a bee sting.
好个勇敢的消防队员
What a brave firefighter.
医生说罗德尼会没事
The doctors tell me Rodney is going to be okay,
只是皮肉之伤
just a flesh wound.
正港的波士顿英雄
A true blue Boston hero.
回到棚内主播，丹
Back to you, Don.
就是这玩意
This is what it's all about.
大家都要抢的东西
That, right there, is what everybody wants.
汉堡王玩具？
A Burger King toy?
把它打开
Open it up.
热热的，是什么？
It's warm. What is it?
电池
A battery.
电池？
A battery?
它的代号是赛佛
It's code-named Zephyr.
这可不是一般的金顶电池
Not your average Duracell.
高能量输出
It's high output.
永远不会耗尽
Never runs out.
“永远”是什么意思？
What do you mean, "never"?
那个小玩意
That little thing there
是自太阳后第一个永久能量来源
is the first perpetual energy source since the sun.
是说手电筒永远不用换电池？
So, what, your flashlight never runs out of juice?
它可提供的电力远超过手电筒所需
It can power a lot more than a flashlight, June.
真的？
Really?
有多大？
How much more?
可供应一个城镇的用电
Small city.
或是大型潜艇
Large submarine.
这是重大成就
It's big.
发明它的人
The guy who invented it
高中才刚毕业
is barely out of high school.
赛门费克
Simon Feck.
我跟另外一名探员被指派…
I was assigned with another agent to
在威奇塔实验室保护他
watch him at a facility, a lab in Wichita.
另一名探员
And the other guy, the agent,
今早来找你的那个人
is the guy who picked you up this morning.
费兹杰罗
Fitzgerald.
几周前，我发现
A couple of weeks ago, I found out
他打算卖掉这个电池
he was going to sell the battery
并杀掉赛门
and kill Simon.
所以我带走赛门
So I got Simon out of there,
安置他在某个安全地方
put him someplace safe
然后去取回电池
and went back for the battery.
可是费兹…
And Fitz
设计我
set me up.
让大家以为我是叛徒
Made it look like I went rogue.
那时我正好撞见你
That's when I met you.
下一步呢？有什么计划？
So, what's next? I mean, what's the plan?
我想我们稍微休息
I think we get some rest,
去接赛门
pick up Simon,
然后送你回去参加你妹的婚礼
and get you back for your sister's wedding.
我是这一行的佼佼者
I'm pretty good at what I do, June.
今晚
And tonight,
我们很安全
we're safe.
以童子军的名誉保证
Scout's honor.
安全无虞？
Safe and secure?
晚安，罗伊
Good night, Roy.
你真的当过童子军？
Were you really a Boy Scout?
鹰级童子军
Eagle Scout.
我是幼年女童军
I was a Brownie.
酷喔
That's cool.
晚安，罗伊
Good night, Roy.
“曼哈顿”
做一些派给大家吃，人人有份
Pies for everybody. Everybody. Everybody gets pies, okay?
但不加冰淇淋
No ice-cream...
你认为呢？她也有参一脚？
So, what do you think? Are we looking at another player?
她只是傀儡，我们都跟她谈过
We're looking at a pawn. I talked to her, so did he.
她有一间修车厂
She owns a garage,
没护照，哪里都没去过
no passport, gone nowhere, been nowhere.
她是个无名小卒
She's a nobody.
你到现在还没抓到人
You've been two steps behind since this began, Fitz.
你确定你有办法搞定这事？
Are you sure someone is not taking you to school?
快点摆平它
Clean this shit up.
“布鲁克林，纽约”
这里是安全藏身处？
This is a safe-house?
赛门！
Simon!
赛门？
Simon?
跟紧我
Stay close.
赛门…
Hey, Simon,
没时间玩游戏了
this is no time to play.
这些是什么？
What is all this?
赛门，他的研究
Simon. It's what he does.
我来迟了，他走了
I'm late, and he's gone.
“罗伊”
“阿尔卑斯山脉”
赛门
Simon.
“火车”
奥地利制
"Made in Austria."
这些人是谁？费兹的人手？
Who are these people? Are they Fitzgerald's guys?
不，是其他人
No, it's other guys.
其他坏人？
Other bad guys?
更坏的家伙
Worse guys.
拿着弹匣
Hold my mags.
更坏的家伙？
Worse guys?
现在我要你仔细听
Now, I need you to listen carefully.
完全照我的话做
Do exactly as I say.
数到3，我会开火找掩护
On three, I'm gonna lay down cover,
然后我们跑到那里的架子
then we're gonna run to those shelves over there.
好
Okay.
-懂吗？ -懂
-Okay? -Yeah.
准备好了？1…
-You ready? -Yeah. -One...
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
抱歉
Sorry.
我慌了
I panicked.
你想要数到几？
What number would you like?
3，3是个好数字
Let's just stick with three, it's good.
好
Okay.
1…2…
One... Two...
Three.
这些人很狡滑
These guys are fancy.
弹匣
Mags.
可能是安东尼奥昆塔那的人马
Could be Antonio Quintana's men.
他是西班牙军火商
He's a Spanish arms dealer.
他也想要电池
He also wants the battery.
准备好了？
Ready?
-走吧 -好
-Let's move. -Okay.
茱恩，茱恩！
June. June!
我们要怎么逃离这里？
How the hell are we gonna get out of here?
赛门人到底在哪里？
And where the hell is Simon?
我还不知道，但他留下讯息
I don't know yet, but he left a message.
讯息？
-A message? -Wait.
我要你在这里等
What I need you to do right now is wait here.
-什么？ -我去找逃生路线
-What? -Yeah. I'm gonna find us a way out.
-我不能在这里等！ -我马上回来
-I can't wait here! -I'll be right back.
等等！罗伊！
Wait! Roy!
拿着这个
Just take this.
罗伊？
Roy?
茱恩？
June?
茱恩！茱恩！茱恩！
June! June! June! June!
茱恩！
June!
拜托别鬼叫我名字了
Please stop saying my name.
你一直叫我名字我会抓狂
You keep saying my name, it's freaking me out.
好，我懂了
-Okay. I understand. -Okay.
-喝这个 -这是什么？
-Drink this. -What is it?
抗毒剂，他们会放出毒气
Brotine-zero. They're gonna smoke us with D-5.
好
Oh, yeah.
你的呢？
Where's yours?
可恶
Oh, shit.
-抱歉 -不
-I'm sorry. -Oh, no.
他们来了
They're coming.
茱恩…
June.
我知道情况看似不妙
I know this looks bad,
但我们几分钟内
but we'll be out of here
就会逃出这里
in a couple of minutes.
我会搞定
I got this.
我们得走了，茱恩
We gotta go, June. Here,
我会帮你
I'll help you.
我们被击中了
We've been hit!
但没大碍
But it's okay!
我们度过这关就脱离困境了
We get through this, we're home free!
准备好…预备…跳！
Ready, set, go!
我们快到了
We're almost there.
你好，懒惰虫
Hey, there, sleepy head.
我昏迷多久了？
How long have I been out?
18小时
Eighteen hours.
我在哪里？
Where am I?
我的窝
My place.
我们在无讯号区
We're off-grid.
从没人能找到这里
No one's ever found me here.
可惜我们不能久待
Shame we can't stay longer.
我们得去找赛门
We got a rendezvous with Simon.
他没事，我解读了他的密码
He's fine. I figured out his code.
他是铁道迷
He's crazy about trains.
他用我给他的护照去奥地利
He used the passport I gave him and went to Austria.
你又对我下药了，罗伊
You drugged me again, Roy.
是啊
Yeah.
你不行这样
You can't do that.
你的抗压性不高
Well, you weren't coping well.
我不确定要是你醒着
I'm not sure, if you were awake,
他们会不会放你一条生路
if they would've even let you live.
我穿着什么？
What am I wearing?
比基尼，我们在热带区
A bikini. We're in the tropics.
我怎么穿上的？
How did I get in the bikini?
茱恩，我曾受训在黑暗中
June, I've been trained to dismantle a bomb in the pitch black
只靠安全别针和薄荷糖拆炸弹
with nothing but a safety pin and a Junior Mint.
我想我能替你穿脱衣服却…
I think I can get you in and out of some clothes without
不瞄一眼
looking.
我不保证没瞄，可是…
I'm not saying that's what I did, but...
好吧
Okay.
抱歉，反射动作
Sorry. Reflex.
我该受罚
I deserved that.
再打我一次
Hit me again.
我不会阻止你
I won't stop you.
茱恩
June.
茱恩？
June?
茱恩！
June!
回纹针和薄荷糖
...paper clips and Junior Mints...
我不保证没瞄
"Not that I'm saying that's what I did."
该死！
Shit!
这是他的手机吗？
Is this his phone?
“移动，警告”
移动，警告
Movement alert.
“艾玛波拉路5826号”
艾玛波拉路…
5826号
Amapola.
那是1967年的庞帝克车款
That's a '67 Grand Prix.
我以为我们应该在无讯号区
I thought we were off the grid.
艾波儿
April.
艾波儿？
April?
艾波儿！我知道！我没事！
April! I know! No, I'm okay!
听着，艾波儿？艾波儿？
Listen, April... April? April?
艾波儿，听到我吗？艾波儿！
April, can you hear me? April!
艾波儿，你能…
April, can you...
我懂，我没事！听着，艾波儿…
I know! No, I'm okay! Listen, April... April?
能听到我吗？
April, can you hear me? April!
米勒在干嘛？
那女的是谁？
我们不清楚，安东尼奥
We don't know, Antonio.
我们追踪她的电话到亚速尔群岛 我们掌握位置了
We traced her phone to the Azores. We're in range now.
在调查局前逮到他们
Get to them before the agency.
你回来的正是时候
Perfect timing.
午餐好了
Lunch is ready.
你一定很渴
You must be thirsty.
这是椰子汁，富有电解质
It's coconut. It's loaded with electrolytes.
冷静，好吗？
Just... Whoa.
冷静
Okay?
可以吗？
Yeah?
好耶！
Yeah!
你有两把刷子呢
Hey. You got skills.
-我爸想生男孩 -是吗？
-My dad wanted boys. -Yeah?
放开我
Let me go.
你想走随时能走
You can get out anytime you want.
我教你
I'll show you.
魔术师的手势
Hands like Houdini.
手掌转向下
Turn your palms down,
连续动作
and all at once,
手甩向地面，屁股往后推
throw your hands to the ground and your hips back.
很好
Nice.
好样的
That was good.
你到底是谁？
Who are you?
讲真的
Really.
这怎么可能
I don't understand.
跟我来
Follow me.
我搞不懂，我没留下线索
I don't understand. I came in clean.
我的手机无法追踪
My phone is secure. It's secure.
除非你打了电话
Unless you made a call.
-但你没打电话 -对，我没打
-And you didn't make a call. -No, I didn't make a call.
我接了电话
I took a call.
你接了电话？
You took a call?
通话时间很短
It was a quick one.
你…
You...
快点
Come on.
我以为我们在无讯号区
I thought we were off the grid,
-然后手机响了 -别紧张
-and then the phone rang. -It's okay.
是我妹，我得接电话
It was my sister and I had to take the call.
小心脚步
Watch your step.
-我不想让她担心 -保持专心
You know? I didn't want her to worry.
不…
No, no, no...
我不行，我不行上去那玩意
I can't get into that. I just can't get into that thing.
我不敢上去
I can't get into that.
-茱恩 -罗伊…
-June. -Roy...
你还是弄昏我好了，什么药都好
Just, please, knock me out. Use broton-seven or whatever.
-别怕 -你抓着我脖子
-It's okay. -You're grabbing my neck.
你要我别对你下药
You asked me not to drug you.
好，很好
Okay, good.
魔术师的手势…
Hands like Houdini. Hands...
罗伊？
Roy?
“开普尔山，阿尔卑斯山脉”
-我感觉不到脸！ -时候到了
-I can't feel my face! -Okay, time.
好，赛门，我们得回去了
Okay, Simon...
罗伊，这东西的拉力…
Roy, the pull on this thing...
-我们说好10分钟 -这东西的牵引力
-We said 10 minutes. -The traction on this thing.
能拉动5万公吨！
It can pull up to 50,000 metric tons!
我懂了
I get it.
这是液压传动柴油车！
It's a diesel hydraulic!
你不想看你的赛佛吗？
Don't you wanna see your Zephyr?
想
Yes.
请问一下
Excuse me.
早安，小姐
Guten Morgen, miss.
能告诉我我们在哪里吗？
Can you tell me where we are?
现在吗？我们在奥地利
Right now, miss? We are in Austria.
奥地利
Austria, huh?
小姐，需要早餐吗？
Would you like some breakfast, miss?
好，太好了
Yeah, that would be great.
谢谢
Thanks.
好，我要煎饼、炒蛋…
Okay, I'm gonna have some pancakes, scrambled eggs...
炒蛋
-Scrambled eggs. ...and...
-配一杯牛奶 -一杯牛奶
-With a glass of milk. -And a glass of milk.
请给我一杯哈维撞墙
Can I get a Harvey Wallbanger, please?
-没问题 -谢谢
Certainly, sir.
“来电，不明号码”
统计上，搭火车的死亡率
You know, statistically, you're a lot more likely to die riding on a train
远高于任何其他种类交通工具
than any other form of transportation.
比坐飞机上高10.3倍
10.3 times more likely than dying on a plane.
赛门？
Simon?
赛门费克？
Simon Feck?
我是
Yes.
我的名字是茱恩
My name is June.
我是罗伊米勒的朋友
I'm a friend of Roy Miller's.
好巧！
Oh!
你有找到他吗？有见到他吗？
Have you found him yet? Have you seen him?
还没
No, not yet.
你不接电话吗？
Don't you wanna answer that?
想
Yeah.
可是不行
But I can't.
我不该接
I'm not supposed to.
可能是罗伊
It might be Roy.
是啊，但他叫我别接电话
Yeah, but he told me not to answer the phone,
因为信号会被追踪
because the signal can be tracked.
没错，当然了
That's right. Of course.
“待在房间，我跟赛门在一起”
罗伊有跟你说接下来的计划吗？
Did Roy happen to tell you about the plan here?
我们该在这里碰面或…
Are we supposed to meet him here, or...
你说那杯调酒叫什么？
What did you say that drink was?
-哈维… -是哈维撞墙
-A Harvey... -It's a Harvey Wallbanger.
帮我点一杯好吗？
Do you mind just ordering me one of those?
看起来很好喝
Because it looks great.
我马上回来，你在这里等一下
I'll just be right back. You just stay here for a second.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
不太对劲
Something is wrong.
电池愈来愈热了，罗伊
It's getting hotter, Roy.
她没接电话
She didn't answer her phone.
-我叫她别接 -我们刚到这里
-I told her not to. That's... -We just got here.
这是好消息
That's good news.
我相信她会出现的，罗伊
I'm sure she'll turn up. Roy...
我贴了纸条给她看
I left a note posted right there.
这可能会是个问题
We may have an issue here.
-温度… -她饿了…她饿了
-The temperature... -She's hungry... She's hungry.
愈来愈热了，我们需要冷却它
It's getting too hot. We need to cool it down.
对，她一定是去找东西吃
Yeah, she went to get something to eat.
很好，来吧，赛门
Good. Come on, Simon.
-需要服务吗？ -是
-May I help you? -Yeah.
我感觉有点晕车
I'm feeling a little bit train-sick.
能待在这里一下吗？
Is it okay if I hang out here for a while?
当然，我拿些水给你
Of course, I will get you some water.
请用
Here you go.
你杀了他
You killed him
不，是你杀的
No, you did
你不看大自然频道的吗？
Have you never watched the Nature Channel?
现在这样就是豹子抓到小鹿
See that's the moment,
小鹿跑了那么久
for so long
终于停步，躺下了
just stops and lies down
这一刻非常真诚，对吧？
that's a very honest moment, don't you see it?
电池在哪里？
Where is the battery?
抱歉，我想找冰块
I'm sorry, I'm looking for ice.
-罗伊 -班哈德
-Roy. -Bernhard.
米勒
Miller.
-真衰 -别担心
-Wrong room. -It's okay. It's okay.
-你认识他？ -对
-You know him? -Yeah.
他是白金级的杀手
He's an assassin, platinum grade.
他来抓赛门的
He's come to collect Simon.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
还有杀你
And to kill you.
那是赛门？
That's Simon?
对，茱恩、赛门，认识一下
-Yeah, June, Simon. Simon, June. -Hi.
老天
Jeez!
没关系，我会搞定
I'm okay. I got this.
赛门，让开
Simon, please move.
你相当有种，小姐
You have quite some balls, Frǎulein.
魔术师的手势
Hands like Houdini.
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
但你想杀我
But you were trying to kill me.
好恶心
That's disgusting.
我的天，快死吧！
Oh, my God. Just die!
该死
Oh, shit.
我得送你们到安全地方
I got to get you guys someplace safe.
“法医”
-他们不在火车上 -是吗？
-They're not on the train. -Oh, really?
上一站的监视器没有照到他们
Cameras at the last station show nothing.
他们一定在半路下车了
They must have gotten off between stops.
当地警方一无所获
Locals haven't found anything.
老爱耍花招，罗伊
Always the classics, Roy.
别动，我5分钟后回来
Stay here, I'll be back in 5
费兹
Fitz
罗伊
Roy
感谢你见我
Thanks for meeting me
感谢你离职
Thanks for the flying
我从那个小圈子看到你时
You know, when I saw you through that little circle,
觉得你在找出口
I saw a man looking for a way out.
我不是说过去几天不够精彩
not telling the last few days haven't been an absolutly spectacular
但我想你该知道事情终会结柬
but I think you know it's all coming to an end
我想你知道 你会害你那个女朋友死掉
I think you know you're gonna get your little lady killed
在我看来，你有几个选择
The way I see it, you have some options
出卖赛门，卖电池
You could sell Simon, you could sell the battery
你出卖他们，就可以脱身
或是你去自首
Or you could turn yourself in
是可以
Could
那是对你关怀的人 最安全的选择
That's the safest option for the people you seemed to cared so much about.
天才男孩不会有事 没人会看到他受伤
The boy genius would be fine. No one wants to see him hurt
那女的呢？
And the girl?
她会回家 她所经历的那场冒险
She goes home, having left her adventure
没人会相信
that no one and her little world will ever believe
喂
Yes
不，我们刚到
No, we just got in.
我们现在不是在说话了？ 不，我了解
Well, we're talking now. No, I understand.
也很高兴听到你的声音，娜欧蜜
Well, it's good to hear your voice, too, Naomi.
我跟你在可普斯碰头 你尽快赶到那里
I'll meet you at the caprice. As soon as you can be there.
这个城市很美吧？
It's a beautiful city, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
没见过这种美景
Never seen anything quite like it.
我也一样
Neither have I.
我得出去一下
I got to go out for a bit.
好
Okay.
我想叫客房服务
I was thinking about ordering some room service.
我想或许我们能共进晚餐
And I thought maybe we could have dinner or something.
听起来很棒
That sounds great.
9点好吗？
9:00?
没问题
9:00 sounds great.
茱恩？
June?
帮个忙待在房里好吗？安全起见
Could you do me a favor and just stick around here? It's better.
当然，我能去哪里？
Oh, yeah, of course. Where else am I gonna go?
待会见
See you in a bit.
他们不会伤害你
They're not gonna hurt you.
你太有价值了
You're too valuable to them.
深呼吸，听你的音乐
Now, just breathe, listen to your music.
拿去，事实上我替你弄到这个
Here, as a matter of fact, I got that for you.
“霍尔与欧兹乐团”
我知道你喜欢他们
I know you like them.
谢了
Cool, thanks.
听着，随你点客房服务
Listen, order as much room service as you like,
但别离开房间
but don't leave the room.
好
Okay.
我晚点需要跟你谈赛佛的事
We need to talk about the Zephyr later.
当然
And we will.
发生了那些事，我不确定你还会来
considering what's happened
生活满有意思的，不是吗？
Life could be funny, isn't it?
我们所做的选择
爱人和朋友
Lovers and friends
失去和找到
Lost and found
你看起来不太一样
You seem different.
是吗？
Do I?
你的同伴是谁？
So, who's your companion?
她很漂亮，那个金发妞
She's beautiful. The blonde.
她似乎很能干
She seems capable.
我刚认识她
I just met her.
她不重要
She's a nobody.
我跟她只是萍水相逢
Just someone I picked up along the way.
太可惜了
That's a shame.
这话题很无趣 我们到底要不要交易？
This is getting boring. Are we gonna do a deal or not?
别用这口气跟我说话
Don't speak to me like that.
我想用什么口气是我的事，东尼
I will speak to you any way I please, Tony.
你运气好才见得到我
We both know you're lucky I'm here.
电池在我手上，我很忙
I have the battery. I'm on a schedule.
世上不缺坏人，大把人要出价
The world is full of bad guys and people are calling.
我了解
I understand.
你的开价？
What's your price?
我心中有个数字
I have a figure in mind.
你们觉得值多少？
What's it worth to you?
罗伊，你不爽你的岛被毁？
Are you angry about your island, Roy?
时间不多了，东尼
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, Tony.
我是伊莎贝拉乔治
I'm Isabel George,
中情局的反间谍部门主管
Director of Counter Espionage at the CIA.
你当然是
I'm sure you are.
原谅我，我…
Forgive me, I just...
我不知道还有什么可以相信
I just don't know exactly what to believe.
这不难理解，过去5天
Well, that's understandable, considering that the last five days
你不断被一名局里叛离的探员
you've been fed a steady diet of misinformation and fantasy
灌输错误情报和幻想
by an agent of ours who's recently gone rogue.
他说费兹杰罗才是想偷电池的人
Well, he said that Fitzgerald was the one that wanted to steal the battery.
我们来检视事实吧
Well, let's examine the facts.
米勒告诉你他在保护赛佛…
Miller told you that he was protecting the Zephyr
被不肖人士滥用
from people wanting to misuse it.
如今他却想卖给一名国际军火商
But now he's trying to sell it to an international arms dealer.
安东尼奥昆塔那
Antonio Quintana.
欧洲最大的武器制造商之一
One of Europe's leading weapons manufacturers.
扪心自问，赫文斯小姐
Ask yourself, Miss Havens,
罗伊米勒有哪句话是实话？
has Roy Miller said anything to you that's proven to be true?
-不好意思 -不，我才抱歉
-God, excuse me. -No, I'm sorry.
我在看手机，我最讨厌别人这么做
Sorry, I was looking at my phone. I hate it when people do that.
我的天啊，真抱歉
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
撞上瘾了
This is getting to be a habit.
是啊
Yeah, it is.
他利用你挟带电池通过安检
He used you as a mule to carry the battery through security,
赫文斯小姐
Miss Havens.
他在玩弄你
He's been playing you.
他是间谍，专门以骗人为业
He's a spy, that's what he does. He lies for a living.
利用爱意、同情…
Any love, empathy,
都是他被训练的项目
we train that right out of them.
你有何遐想？
What did you imagine?
你们两人住在一起，养只狗
The two of you would move into a condo together, get a dog?
你不可能跟他生活，那是幻想
You can't have a life with him. That's fantasy.
不过你能恢复原本生活
But you can have yours back.
她离开8分钟了
She's been gone eight minutes.
我们需要你在米勒之前回到饭店
We need you to get back to the hotel before Miller.
我该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
这样吧
All right, then.
这只笔是发送器
This pen is a transmitter.
一旦你确认米勒没藏着赛佛
Once you have confirmation that Miller has not hidden the Zephyr,
在附近某处或他身上
that it's somewhere nearby, or on his person,
按下顶端的按钮通知我们
you can confirm this by simply clicking the top button.
抱歉，我晚了
I'm sorry I'm late.
一切顺利吧
Everything go okay?
还不错
Well enough.
电池愈来愈热了
It's getting hotter.
所以你谈好价钱了？
So, did you get your price?
我今晚跟踪你
I followed you tonight.
你无话可说？
You have nothing to say?
敬威奇塔
Here's to Wichita
我们第一次…
where we first...
撞出火花的地方
Bumped into each other.
你觉得那是命运吗？
Do you think that was fate, Roy?
我不相信命运
I don't believe in fate.
但我相信运气
But I believe in luck.
我不知道该相信什么
I don't know what to believe.
没想到我会这么心痛
That hurt more than I thought it would.
我要回家了
I'm going home.
他们承诺只要你自首，就会保护你
They promised that if you turned yourself in, they'd protect you.
我欣赏你的乐观
I love your optimism.
保持下去
Never lose it.
带她出去
Get her out of here.
他不在这里
He's not here, sir.
他们有说会送你回家吗？
Did they tell you you're going home?
你知道太多内幕了，茱恩！
You've seen the inside of the honeycomb, June!
你不能回家
You can't go home.
嫌犯在屋顶上
The suspect is on the roof.
该死
Oh, shit.
乔治小姐！
Director George!
带她上车
Get her in the car.
他逃往河边
He's heading toward the river.
别开枪！电池在他身上！
Stand down! He has the battery!
嘿！停止！
Hey! Hey! Hold it!
停火！
Hold your fire!
别开枪！
Stand down!
电池在他身上！
He has the battery!
那小子在我们手上吗？
Did you secure the kid?
对
Yeah.
有发现罗伊吗？
Did they find Roy?
我们会找出尸体，一定要
We'll find the body. We have to.
他带着赛佛沉入河底
He went down with the Zephyr.
班和我想感谢各位前来
Ben and I would like to thank all of you for coming
我特别要感谢我姊姊茱恩
and I'd like to say special thanks to my sister June
各位都知道她参加过 《全美通缉令》
who many of you will recognize from "American's most wanted"
谢谢大家
Thank you
不只今晚帮了我 每天晚上也都一样
Not just for helping me with tonight, but for helping me every night
我知道这或许不是 你想要的生活
I know that it wasn't always the way you probably in vision
你放弃了这许多 好让我过我想要的生活
You gave up so much that, I could have the life I wanted
敬你
A toast
希望将来茱恩的发展 可以赶上艾波儿
Here's to a year, when June comes before April
谢谢
Thank you
“史威德巴，德国”
费兹？
Fitz?
我想我们转错弯了 拉姆史坦应该往西
Fitz, I think we just made a wrong turn. Ramstein is that way, west.
我们现在是往南
I think we're going south.
没错，你说对了
You know what? You're right.
转告他我们重回正轨
Tell him we're back on track.
我没拿到电池，但其他人也没机会
I don't have the battery, but no one's gonna get it now.
对，制造者在我手上
Yeah, I've got the next best thing.
两天后西班牙见
I'll see you in Spain in two days.
嗨，威尔莫
Hey, Wilmer.
婚礼顺利吗？ -很顺利
-How was the party? -It was nice.
-我看到那台古董车还在 -是啊
-I see the goat is still out there. -Yeah.
我以为是结婚礼物
I thought it was a wedding present.
原本是，不过…
It was, but,
我想她不是那么想要我送她
I think I wanted her to want it more than she wanted it.
好吧
Okay.
我想我会送她房子
I think I'm gonna give her the house
哇
Wow
我是说
I mean
她和班需要有自己的家
She and Ben need a place of their own
你真好
That's nice
波士顿的经典摇滚电台 接下来是国王人马乐团
... Boston's classic rock station. Here are the Kingsmen.
这车刚送来吗？
This just come in?
G款格兰披治，史上最长车盖
G-body Grand Prix. Longest hood in history.
整理好会超漂亮
Gonna be a real beaut.
鲁玛…费玛…？不对…
Ru-pa... Fee-pa... No, it's...
是艾玛波拉路5826号
5826 Amapola.
离这里1小时车程
That's like an hour from here.
或许是安全藏身处
Maybe it's a safe-house.
好戏上场
Here we go.
“奈特府”
糟了！
Shit!
谁在外头？我真的会开枪
Who's out there? I'm not afraid to use this.
法兰克，看看她
Oh, Frank, look at her!
我想知道她半夜在我草坪上干嘛
I want to know what she's doing on my lawn in the middle of the night.
我送来你订的活塞
I... I have the pistons you ordered.
活塞？
Pistons?
1967年格兰披治车款用的
For the '67 Grand Prix.
莫莉，我没有…
Molly, I didn't...
你全身湿透了，请进来
You are all wet. Please, come inside.
法兰克，车库外那台庞帝克很经典
That Pontiac you have out there, Frank, is a real classic.
我超爱1970前出厂的格兰披治
I really love pre-'70s Grand Prixs.
你们住在这里很久了吗？
So, you two lived here long?
这间老房子？这是我们40年的家了
This old place? It's been our home for 40 years.
请坐，吃片饼干
Sit down, honey. Have a cookie.
法兰克认为我们该搬家，但我住惯了
Frank thinks we should move, but you know what? I am comfortable.
况且我们住得起
And we can afford to stay,
多亏杂志的抽奖
thanks to Publishers Clearing House.
你们中奖过？
You won Publishers Clearing House?
两次
Twice.
还有中两次乐透的快选奖
Plus, we won two lotto quick picks
法兰克甚至不记得有买
Frank doesn't even remember buying.
因为我根本没买
Because I didn't buy them.
是啊，就像你没上网订活塞
Oh, yeah, like you didn't order pistons off the Internet.
你最好忘记自己在输入电脑什么
You don't know what you're typing into that computer, Frank.
再等几分钟衣服就会干
Another couple of minutes on your clothes, honey.
所以…
So,
罗伊米勒
Roy Miller.
这里是他的安全藏身处之一吧？
This was one of his safe-houses, wasn't it?
你在说什么？
What in the hell are you talking about?
这究竟是怎么一回事？
Honey, what's this all about?
抱歉，我以为…
I'm sorry, I just thought, maybe...
我一定完全搞错了
I must've had this all wrong.
我想打听我朋友罗伊的消息
I was just looking for some information about my friend, Roy.
想换衣服的话，化妆室在那边
If you'd like to change, there's a powder room right there.
那是我们的儿子马修
That's our son, Matthew.
在科威特的直升机事故身亡
We lost him in Kuwait. There was a chopper crash.
他救了两名同袍的性命
He saved the lives of two of his crewmen, and...
他总是会照顾人
He just always took care of everyone.
他是鹰级童子军
He was an Eagle Scout.
这张是他游泳比赛领奖时拍的
This was taken the day he got that swimming badge.
他可以游过萨纳比湖
He could swim clear across Lake Sunapee
几乎不需要换气
with practically one breath.
我实在…
I just...
我太失礼了
I've been terribly rude.
我是茱恩赫文斯
I'm June Havens.
莫莉奈特
Molly Knight.
我是茱恩赫文斯
This is June Havens,
我留言在自己的电话
and I'm leaving a message on my own machine
给监听电话的人
for whoever is listening to this phone call.
赛佛在我手上
I have the Zephyr.
赛佛在我这里，我准备好谈交易
I have the Zephyr, and I'm ready to make a deal.
我在28号公路旁
I'm sitting on Route 28,
就在新罕布夏州
right outside New Hampshire.
如果你想要赛佛
And if you want the Zephyr,
快点来拿吧
you better come and get it.
嗨，大伙儿
Hey, fellas.
所以…
So,
你们想要赛佛吗？
you want the Zephyr?
电池就在我这里
I got the Zephyr. It's right here.
过来拿吧
Come and get it.
“塞维尔，西班牙”
拜托
Come on.
让开！
Let's go!
-好痛！ -欢迎来到西班牙
Welcome to Espana.
今天是圣佛明奔牛节
Today is the festival of San Fermin.
赫文斯小姐，你看过斗牛吗？
Have you ever seen a bullfight, Miss Havens?
我是安东尼奥昆塔那
My name is Antonio Quintana.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我被下了什么药？
What did he give me?
是我公司正在研发的药
It's something we're developing at my company.
新开发的吐真药
A new kind of truth serum.
是吗？
Really?
我有几个电池的问题要问你
I have a few questions for you about the battery,
因为我们都知道你耍了我的人
since we both know what you gave to my men was a joke.
我看你超不顺眼！
I don't like you very much.
真心话！
The truth!
很好
Good!
我倒是很喜欢米勒
You know, I really like Miller, though.
我在萨尔斯堡完全错怪他了
'Cause, you know, I was totally wrong about him in Salzburg.
他要我听到那通电话好跟踪他
He wanted me to hear that phone call so that I would follow him.
我供出他，他就能让我安全回家
I'd turn him in, and then he could get me home safely.
他是为了保护我
He was trying to protect me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
很瞎的是…
It's crazy that
我在他身边感到坚强又能干
I could feel so powerful and capable around him...
闭嘴
-Shut up.
同时他也会照顾我
...and yet he takes care of me.
闭嘴
Shut up!
电池在哪里？在哪里？
Where is the battery? Where is it?
我敢说你从没替女生煎蛋卷
I bet you've never made a girl an omelet,
对吧，安东尼奥？
have you, Antonio?
别惹火我，茱恩
Don't test me, June.
或者及时送女生参加老妹的婚礼
Or got her to her sister's wedding on time.
老实说这些都是小事
It's really the little things, honestly.
不过却意义非凡
But they count so much.
够了！
Enough!
好！
Okay!
米勒死了！
Miller is dead!
罗伊米勒死了，他出局了！
Roy Miller is dead, he's out.
不对
No.
他没死，他能憋气非常久
No, he's not. He can hold his breath for a really long time.
他死了！
He is dead!
我问你最后一遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.
要是你不告诉我实话
But if you don't tell me what I need to know,
你就死定了！
you're gonna die!
我不知道电池在哪里
I don't know where the battery is.
那你干嘛到处宣称你有？
Then why did you tell everyone you had it? Why?
因为我想找到罗伊
Because I was trying to find Roy.
安东尼奥，每当你这种坏人出现
Well, Antonio, whenever there's bad guys like you around,
罗伊就会在附近
Roy's not too far away.
你死定了
You're gonna die.
终于！
Finally!
幸会，约翰
Nice to meet you, John.
安东尼奥
Antonio.
你没拿到电池太可惜了
Too bad you couldn't get the battery.
那小子呢？
Where is the boy?
你不会以为我会直接带来吧？
You didn't think I'd just bring the package, did you?
带着钱跟着我到河边
Why don't you follow me down to the river and bring the money?
好
Okay.
这是盖草屋顶吗？我以前从没看过
Is this thatching in here? Because I've never seen anything like that before.
波士顿有一些很旧的建筑
We have really old architecture in Boston,
但没有像这样的
but nothing like this.
你真走运，因为这地方…
You're really lucky, because this place is...
听我说，你真走运，这里真美
Let me tell you. You're really lucky, it's beautiful here.
现在我的思绪好清晰
My thoughts are so clear.
这里靠军火收入还是家产盖的？
Is this all weapons money, or is this family money?
花园！
Gardens!
他喜欢花园吗？
He likes gardens, huh?
你们会园艺吗？
Do you guys ever do any gardening?
可放松心情，棒极了
It's really relaxing. It's amazing how much you can just...
这里真令人开心，瞧这些喇叭花
This really is a happy place. Look at these trumpet flowers. They...
艾德华多，不必老是拉着我
Okay, Eduardo, you don't have to pull me around.
干脆直接告诉我要去哪里
You can just tell me where you want me to go, okay?
这边，金发妞
This way, blondie.
看吧？我们终于在沟通了
See? Now we're communicating.
你应该是要带我去安全无虞的地方
I bet you're taking me someplace safe and secure.
特别地方，安东尼奥的特别处所
Someplace special. Antonio's special place.
安东尼奥有特别处所？真好
Antonio has a special place? That's so nice.
每个人都该有特别处所
Everyone should have a special place.
路易斯？
Luis?
艾德华多，有问题吗？
Is there a problem, Eduardo?
-嗨，罗伊 -嗨，茱恩
-Hi, Roy. -Hi, June.
你应该在家里
You're supposed to be home.
-你应该挂了 -我能解释
-You're supposed to be dead. -I can explain.
-不必解释 -我来这里救赛门
-You don't have to. -I came here to get Simon.
我刚追踪到他
I just, you know, caught up with him.
很好
That's cool.
他叫做艾德华多
His name is Eduardo. Eduardo.
我要你听好
I need you to listen,
因为你醒来时
because when you wake up,
你要打给你老板告诉他
you're gonna call your boss and you're gonna tell him
罗伊米勒，就是我
that Roy Miller, that's me,
我拿到电池并跟这美眉逃了
has the battery and escaped with the girl.
-你拿到电池了？ -对
-You have the battery? -Yeah.
你告诉他下一个就是他
You tell him I'm coming for him.
-了没？ -了
-Yes. -Okay.
我们走
Let's go.
我担心赛门，我还没见到他
I'm worried about Simon. I haven't seen him.
我的追踪系统断断续续
My tracker has been spotty.
跟你生活好刺激！
Life with you is so exciting.
你令我兴奋，米勒！
You excite me, Miller.
我太晚到了
I took too long to get here.
-7点钟方向 -什么？
-7:00. -What?
7点钟方向
7:00.
我想要炒饭
I think I feel like having sex.
我们炒饭一定很过瘾
I think we'd have really great sex.
他们有给你下药吗？
Did they give you something?
你该多补充水分
You should hydrate.
罗伊？
Roy?
罗伊
Roy.
罗伊？
Roy?
茱恩
June.
茱恩？
June?
你见到我似乎没有很开心
You don't seem very happy to see me, Roy.
什么？
What?
你反应冷淡
Not really.
我很开心
I am happy.
-这红点是我们？ -不，我们是黄点
-So the red dot is us? -No, we're yellow.
红点是赛门
The red dot is Simon.
快点！快点！
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
-该当空中飞人了 -空中飞人？
-Air time. -Air time?
他说他的名字是罗伊米勒 他说电池在他那
He says his name is Roy Miller. He says he has the battery.
米勒追来了
Miller is here.
他在那里！
There he is!
这边，跟着我！
This way. Follow me!
斗牛？
Bulls?
-是费兹！ -我看到他了
-There's Fitz! -I see him.
天啊
Oh my god!
他们死了
罗伊！罗伊！罗伊！
Roy, Roy, Roy
上面
Up there
-往哪里走？ -不知道，失去讯号了
-Which way? -I don't know. We lost the signal.
-拿着枪 -好
-Take the guns. -Okay.
坐前面
Here.
-接着呢？ -让他们吃子弹
-What next? -Let them have it.
弹匣
Mags
茱恩赫文斯，你真有两把刷子
June Havens, you've got skills.
我们走！
Let's go!
好
Go.
下面见
See you down there.
-你确定？ -拼了
Are you sure?
不好意思
Sorry.
-起来 -好
-Get up. -Okay.
别动，罗伊！
Freeze right there, Roy!
嗨，赛门
Hey, Simon.
快跪下！
Get down on your knees, now!
罗伊！
-Roy! -Now! Now!
把枪丢入水中
Put them in the water. In the water.
我只要这孩子，费兹
I just want the kid, Fitz.
希望你带来我要的东西
Well, I hope you brought what I want,
否则我就得杀了他
otherwise I'm gonna have to kill him.
我向你保证，我会下手
And I swear to you, I'll do it.
我相信你，在威奇塔就见识过
I believe you. Just like Wichita.
-我了解 -好
-I understand. -Okay.
我只是要拿电池
I'm just gonna get the battery.
别给他，罗伊
-It's right here. -Don't give it to him, Roy.
拜托别给他，不要
Please don't give it to him. No, no.
拜托别给他
Roy, Roy, please don't give it to him.
放在甲板上
Put it on the deck.
罗伊…拜托别给他！
-Roy, Roy, please don't give it to him! -Easy, easy.
赛门，别紧张
Simon, it's okay.
罗伊，别给他！
Roy, don't give it to him!
闭嘴！嗦！
-Shut it! Stop it! Shut it! -Roy!
好吧，我会再作一个
Okay. Okay, I'll make another one.
-你不懂 -赛门，别说了
-You don't understand. -Simon, don't talk.
我会再作一个
I'll just make another one.
再作一个？
Make another one?
我快死了吗？
Am I dying?
不，你只是昏倒了
No, you fainted.
-对不起 -没关系
-I'm sorry. -No, that's okay.
不，我一直试着告诉你
No, no. I've been trying to tell you...
为什么很热？
Why is it hot?
因为它充满能量
Because it's filled with power.
那个电池…我搞砸了 它的状况正在恶化
The battery... I messed up. It's deteriorating.
我知道，很不稳定
I know. It's unstable.
你真天才，赛门
You're a smart guy, Simon.
你一定会想出解决之道
I know you'll figure it out.
我的眼镜，谢谢
Oh, my glasses. Thank you.
罗伊…
Roy,
你中枪了
you're shot.
找人帮忙
Get help.
罗伊
Roy.
你好美，茱恩赫文斯
You're beautiful, June Havens.
保持清醒，罗伊，看着我
Stay with me. Roy, look at me.
保持清醒
Stay with me.
我们来了，米勒，我们会救你…
We're here now, Miller. We got you. We got you.
-充电到360 -茱恩…
-Charge at 360. -June.
清空！
Clear!
“华府”
这几周真是慌乱，米勒
It's been a spectacular couple of weeks, Miller.
很高兴见到你，伊莎贝拉
It's good to see you, Isabel.
嗨，各位
Hi, guys.
你清理了门户，罗伊
You cleaned house, Roy.
这点我得谢谢你
I have to thank you for that.
我信任错人了
I trusted the wrong man.
这是难免的
It happens.
赛门很开心，他有新的实验室
Simon's happy. He's got a new lab.
茱恩呢？
Where is June?
我送她回家了
I sent her home.
她了解状况了
She gets it.
她明白你俩的生活天差地别 她会继续过日子
She knows you two lead different lives and she's moving on.
你也该这样
As should you.
你早放弃了这一切羁绊
You gave up those things.
抛开身分、家人、朋友 这是工作的一部分
You let go of who you were. Family, friends, that's the deal.
我们干嘛还谈这种事？
Why are we still talking about this?
因为你是调查局的重要资产
Because the agency invested a lot in you.
你唯有心无旁骛才有价值
And you're an asset only as long as you stay focused.
你的气色很好
You look good.
好好休息
Get some rest.
我们明天得把你转到安全的地方 为了你的安全起见
We got to transfer you to a secure facility tomorrow. For your safety.
护士，什么… 你给我什么？
Nurse? What... What did you give me?
抗毒剂
Brotine-zero.
别乱动，罗伊
Stay under there, Roy.
你要装死
You're dead.
请借过
Make way, please.
去太平间
Going to the mortuary.
别担心，罗伊，我会搞定
Don't worry, Roy. I got this.
渡假时间到了
It's time for a vacation.
乘风飞翔
Ride like the wind
我要行经漫漫长路
And I've got
到达墨西哥边界
Such a long way to go To make it to the border of Mexico
你好，懒惰虫！
Hey, there, sleepy head.
今天是哪一天？
What day is it?
有朝一日
Someday.
有朝一日，罗伊
Someday, Roy.
我穿着什么？
What am I wearing?
海滩裤
A pair of shorts.
我怎么穿上的？
How did I get into shorts?
我曾受训徒手重组六速传动箱
Roy, I've been trained to rebuild a six-speed transmission
只靠钳子和活动扳手
with nothing but a pair of pliers and a crescent wrench.
我想我能替你穿海滩裤却不瞄一眼
I think I can get you into a pair of shorts without looking.
但我不保证没瞄
I'm not saying that's what I did.
你负责带路和播歌
You're both the navigator and the DJ.
我们到合恩角有一段漫长的路
And we have a long way to go to Cape Horn.
跟着我
With me
不跟我
without me.
跟着我
With me,
不跟我
without me.
跟着你
With you.
来点好听的音乐吧，DJ先生
Put some tunes on the radio, Mr. DJ.
是，女士
Yes, ma'am.
“麻州”
“合恩角”
我的天啊，法兰克
Oh, my God, Frank.
信封里怎么有去合恩角的机票？
What is this envelope with tickets to Cape Horn?
你在胡说什么？
What are you talking about?
你订机票去南美？
Did you order tickets to South America?
莫莉，我没订机票去任何地方
Molly, I didn't order tickets to anywhere.
你最好忘记自己在输入电脑什么
You don't know what you're typing on that computer, Frank.
-莫莉… -那我们一定又中奖了！
-Molly... -Then, we must've won them!
-莫莉… -我们要去，对吧？
-Molly... -Well, we're going, aren't we?